We're already displaying the correct image, which is this Android party
既に正しい画像である Android party を表示しているので
image, so there's no need to change the source attribute.
ソース属性はこのままで結構です
Similarly, the position isn't really incorrect.
位置もよさそうですね
The image just needs to be larger, so
この画像を大きくしたいだけなので
all of these layout aligned parent attributes, we're not going to use them.
レイアウトを整列するための 親属性は使いません
Using the id attribute in and
id 属性を使うと
of itself doesn't actually make any changes to the layout.
それだけではレイアウトの 変更は何も起こりません
It just give the view a name so that you can refer to it later.
ビューに名前を付けて 後で参照できるだけです
Now there's actually a way to use the background attribute to achieve
background 属性を使って
the effect we're trying to achieve.
必要な効果を目指しましょう
But it doesn't involve an image view.
しかし これにはイメージビューを 必要としません
So if you chose background, you're technically correct, but
background を選ぶことは 技術的には正しいのですが
we're going to go about it in a different way.
別の方法を取りましょう
The way that we learned about in the lesson.
レッスンで学んだ方法です
This leaves us with layout_height, layout_width, and ScaleType.
layout_height と layout_width ScaleType が残っています
ScaleType will change the size of the image within the view box that
ScaleType では 画像の周りにある ビューボックス内にある
surrounds it.
画像のサイズを変更します
While layout_width and
一方 layout_width と
layout_height will actually change the size of that view box.
layout_height は ビューボックスのサイズを変更します
In this case, the image is large enough that the view box expands to fill
今回は wrap_content であれ match_parent であれ
the entire screen no matter if it's wrapped content or matched parent.
ビューボックスを画面全体に広げるのに 画像の大きさは十分です
Because it doesn't matter in this particular case
その理由は 今回の場合
whether we put matched parent or
match_parent や wrap_contentであれ
That said, because we are trying to get the view to expand to the entire screen,
画面全体にビューを 拡大しようとしているので
it would probably be good to set these explicitly as match parent.
match_parentで 設定するとよいでしょう
Then, if we end up using a smaller image,
小さな画像を使用する場合でも
it will still expand to fill the entire screen.
画面いっぱいに広げられます
But while layout height and layout width are sort of optional in this case,
今回はあくまで高さと幅はオプションで
scale type is the actual attribute that you're absolutely going to need to use
ScaleType こそが 実際に使用する属性です
to make the image fill the entire screen.
これを使って画面全体に表示をします
The question is, we've chosen the attribute, but
ここで問題になるのは 属性は選べたものの
we don't know the value to set scale type to.
ScaleType の値が 分からないことです
And that's what I want you to figure out in the next question.
これが 次の問題です